[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Дит. садок' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "幼稚園"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ботанічний сад' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "植物園"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Парк розваг' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "遊園地"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Храм (буддійський)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お寺"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Овочевий' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "八百屋"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Спортзал' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "体育館"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Посольство' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "大使館"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Пожежна станція' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "消防署"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відділ поліції' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "警察署"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Музей' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "博物館"
    }
]
